(Sheldon:)Seattle.
(Leonard:)How were they?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I have no idea.
(Sheldon:)I never left
the train station.
Hang on. You traveled
across the entire country
(Leonard:)and never left a train station?
(Sheldon:)Why would I?
(Sheldon:)That's where
all the cool trains are.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, so you
never went outside?
(Sheldon:)Or had a single
piece of fruit.
(Man:)So...
(Dan:)why do you think
you'd make
(Dan:)a good pharmaceutical sales rep?
(Penny:)Well, I'm a people person.
Mm-hmm.
(Penny:)People like me.
Some of my favorite people
are people.
(Penny:)I feel like I'm saying
"people" a lot.
People, people, people, pe...
Okay, I'm done.
(Dan:)You sure?
(Penny:)People.
(Sheldon:)Yes.
Good!
(Dan:)So, how do you feel
(Dan:)your previous job experience
has prepared you
(Dan:)for a career like this?
(Penny:)Uh, well, as a waitress,
sales was a big part of my job.
(Penny:)I mean, believe me, I convinced
a lot of very large customers,